维罗
Willow.
你可以放下他了
You can put him down now.
哦  我没意识到我抱着他
Oh, I didn't realize.
这感觉太美好了
It just feels so right.
谢谢你
Thank you.
狠狠地处罚玛蒂吧  妈妈
Punish Maddie, mom.
让她刷厕所连刷五年吧
Make her clean the bathrooms for the next five years.
对  处罚她
Yeah, punish her.
你们厕所的确还需要个帮手
Your bathrooms could use a little help.
我们一家六口住在房子里
There are six of us living in one house.
我已经尽我所能了
I do the best I can.
玛蒂  我听见的就是
Maddie, what I'm hearing
你哥哥和你极度专一的好朋友
is that your brother and your overly critical best friend
都自然而然的很不高兴
are understandably upset.
维罗  我只是想帮助你
Willow, I was really just trying to help.
我不想让我最好的朋友
I didn't want to see my best friend
整天对着一个傻小子神魂颠倒
drive herself crazy over some stupid guy.
呃  那个傻小子就坐在这儿呢
Um... The stupid guy is right here.
谢谢  玛蒂  但你不应该插手这件事
Thanks, Maddie, but you shouldn't have interfered.
我知道
I know.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
但你是个好姑娘
But you're a great girl
根本就不需要让一个男的来左右你的情绪
who so does not need a guy to make her feel better about herself.
千万别忘了
Never forget that.
你不会真的不打垒球了吧  对吗
You're not really quitting softball, are you?
不会的  你说得对
No, you're right.
我们要冲校队名额了
We're making varsity.
我不应该对一个傻小子牵挂这么久的
I shouldn't get hung up on what some stupid guy thinks.
又来  我在这儿呢
Again, right here.
所以玛蒂  你有什么想对你弟弟说的吗
So Maddie, is there anything you would like to say to your brother?
好的  乔伊
Yeah. Joey...
今早是你吃了最后那块松饼吗
Did you eat the last muffin this morning?
玛蒂
Maddie.
呃  我不应该让维罗
Uh... I should not have let
咬定了你暗恋她
Willow think that you were her secret admirer.
对极了
Exactly.
我和维罗彼此之间的感情问题
How Willow and I feel about each other
不关你任何事
is none of your business.
噢  不
Oh, no.
乔伊刚刚说了我们之间
Joey just said he and I had feelings...
对彼此有感情啊
About each other.
呃  不对
Um, no.
我的意思是  我先走了算了
What I meant was... I'm going now.
顺便  玛蒂  最后一块松饼是我吃的
And Maddie, I did eat that muffin.